YAE NOGUCHI KEISEI TRANSPORTATION
（野口也英，熒星交通）
Someone once said
曾經有人說過
life is like a jigsaw puzzle.
人生就像拼圖遊戲
From our best memories
所有美好的回憶
to the horrible experiences we want to curse fate for
所有讓你恨不得詛咒上天的可怕經歷
are all irreplaceable pieces of our lives.
都是可以替換的一片片人生拼圖
A lost ticket,
一張丟失的門票
a dress worn in December,
一件在12月穿的洋裝
Thank you.
非常感謝
A stain from an ink called "Blue Hour."
“藍色時光”墨水留下的一滴印
An intimate moment on a winter beach.
冬日海灘上的親密一刻
A Mars rover with your name on it.
一輛寫著你名字的火星探測車
A pop star your own age.
一個和你年齡相仿的流行歌手
Dreams that never came true.
永遠無法實現的夢想
Failed romances.
失敗的戀情
Those who drifted away.
那些漸行漸遠的人
Even those fateful mistakes,
命中註定的錯誤
are they filling up my picture?
也填滿了我的人生嗎？
Good morning, everyone.
大家早安
This is Norn Airlines flight 627 bound for Reykjavik.
本次航班是諾恩航空 飛往雷克雅維克的627航班
This is flight 627.
本次班機為627航班
I'll be your--
我將擔任大家的…
Morning, Yae.
也英早啊
Good morning.
早安
-Have a good day. -Thank you.
-一路順風 -謝謝
I'll be your cabin assistant, Yae Noguchi.
我是今天的空服員野口也英
According to forecasts, the weather should be fair for most of the flight,
天氣預報顯示 航班期間天氣情況大致良好
but please remain in your seats
但請大家留在座位上
with your seatbelts fastened in case of sudden turbulence.
繫好安全帶，以防突然發生亂流
Please get to Mr. Okada at the entrance of Tanukikoji 3-chome.
請到狸小路商店街 三丁目入口處接岡田先生
232, copy.
232收到
What would my life be now
如果從來沒有遇見過你
if I had never met you?
我的人生現在會是什麼樣子？
Yae! Morning!
也英！早安！
Morning.
早安
-I like mild curry. -Let's have spicy!
-我喜歡微辣咖哩 -我們吃大辣的吧！
Crap, it's Wakui!
可惡，是久井！
This goes on your record.
我會給你們記過的
-Oh, crap! -Just act natural.
-該死！ -表現得自然點
You, freshmen! Come here!
新生，過來！
For real?
真的要這樣嗎？
Hurry it up. I can see your knees!
快點，我都能看到妳們的膝蓋了！
Fix it already!
趕緊把裙子放下來！
-Out of the way! -Don't try to hide it.
-讓開！ -別想著混過去
Namiki!
並木！
Come on! Come on!
來啊！
Thank God!
謝天謝地！
Thank you.
謝謝
Obuchi asked me.
是小淵叫我來的
It's Namiki, right?
你是並木同學吧？
Have we met somewhere before?
我們之前是不是在什麼地方見過？
I got it!
我想起來了！
You're the one who spilled the soda at Seicomart.
在精工超市弄灑汽水的是你對吧？
Nope, that wasn't me.
不是，那不是我
Thanks.
謝謝
Later.
晚點見
Thanks for that, Noguchi. You carry that by yourself?
野口同學，謝謝妳啊 是妳自己拿過來的嗎？
Namiki did.
並木同學拿過來的
I see.
這樣啊
He's a pretty good guy.
他可真是個好人
Didn't you ask him to?
不是老師您讓他來拿的嗎？
Me?
我？
What did I do?
我叫他幹什麼？
Nothing.
沒什麼
…is A.
是A
Which means B equals R.
也就是說B等於R
We can put A and B on the x-axis, so we draw them in.
我們可以把A和B 寫在X軸上，把它們寫下來
A, B…
A、B…
Kosaka?
向阪同學
Yes?
在
You'll have exams soon. Make sure you focus.
你們快要考試了，要專心聽課
I'm sorry, sir.
對不起
A,H is perpendicular to the x-axis, so…
A、H垂直於X軸，所以…
So that girl from the other day.
前幾天那個姑娘
From the app?
應用程式上的那個？
She's 28 and works at a call center.
她今年28歲，在客服中心工作
A temp who has to sit there and get yelled at by customers six days a week.
一週六天都要坐在那裡 被客戶訓斥的一個臨時工
Know how to bag a girl like that?
知道要怎麼追這樣的女孩嗎？
Mirroring.
鏡像反射
The girl and the customers are starving for empathy.
那個女孩和客戶都渴望得到共鳴
What do you mean?
這話是什麼意思？
I'm exhausted, I had the worst customer today.
我累死了，今天遇到了最差勁的客戶
Oh, you poor thing.
你真是可憐啊
I feel like wine.
我好想喝酒
Oh wow. Me too.
天啊，我也想
Really?
真的嗎？
When the girl goes to drink, you do too
如果女生去喝酒，你也要一起去
and place your glass down at the same time.
然後你們要同時放下酒杯
After she experiences a moment of peace,
在她感受到片刻的安寧之後
she'll be on top of you 30 minutes later.
再過半個小時她就會騎到你身上了
Good work today.
今天辛苦了
Ah, I'm tired…
好累…
It especially works on ladies over 35 who are tired of the dating game.
這個辦法尤其適用於 受夠約會遊戲的35歲以上歐巴桑
You ran late today.
妳今天跑夜班車啊
Thanks.
謝謝
I thought the rain would bring in a bit more business.
我還以為下雨能多帶來點生意呢
Yeah, totally.
可不是嘛
But I got lucky to get two long rides during surcharge time.
不過我很幸運 在額外收費時段跑了兩趟長途
That's certainly lucky.
確實很幸運
Hold on…
等等…
We're in sync.
我們動作同步了
Is that mirroring?
這就叫“鏡像反射”嗎？
I heard it from Mr. Togashi.
我聽到富樫先生這麼說了
It's pretty obvious.
這樣也太明顯了
Um… Want to grab some dinner?
妳想一起吃晚飯嗎？
It'd be my treat since it's payday.
今天發薪水，我請客
Sorry, I have plans.
抱歉，我已經有安排了
No, no, no.
不是的
I swear that was a coincidence.
我發誓這真的是巧合，真的
It wasn't on purpose.
真的不是故意的
No, no…
不是的
I'm home.
我回來了
Welcome home.
歡迎回家
To those waking up or going to bed, good morning!
正要起床 或是正要上床睡覺的朋友們早安！
Good morning.
早安
It's 5:00 a.m., Saturday, June 16th.
現在是6月16日 星期六，早上5點
It's rather overcast in Sapporo today.
今天札幌的天氣相當陰沉
Yes, the temperatures are low, and it feels quite chilly.
是的，溫度很低，感覺非常冷
Inti Raymi, one of the major religious ceremonies in South America,
南美洲最重要的宗教慶典太陽節
will be held in Peru next week.
下周將在秘魯舉行
Inti Raymi is a festival that will be held on the 24th this month at Cusco…
太陽節是將於本月24日 在庫斯科舉辦的節日慶典…
Inti Raymi.
太陽節
…important ceremony held since the days of the Incan Empire
…是自印加帝國時期以來 所舉辦的重要慶典活動
to welcome the sun god.
目的是迎接太陽神
PERU CUSCO
（秘魯，庫斯科）
In Quechua, Inti means sun and Raymi means festival.
蓋丘亞語中“Inti”意味著太陽 “Raymi”意味著節日
Cusco…
庫斯科…
Cusco's so far.
庫斯科好遠啊
Inti Raymi looks awesome.
太陽節看起來好棒
PLEASE ENTER DEPOSIT AMOUNT
（請輸入存入金額）
TRANSACTION HISTORY TO YUKIHITO KOSAKA
（轉帳紀錄，收款人向阪行人）
Yes.
對
Okay, got it.
啊，找到了
I'll send it tomorrow.
我明天會送過去
Okay, bye.
好的，再見
That's Mr. Kota's, isn't it?
是不是宏大老師的東西？
I can do that for you.
我可以替你送過去
Abiko won't be coming again.
安孫子老師不會再來了
He's busy with training, so I arranged for a different tutor.
他要忙著培訓 所以我請了另一位家教來
He didn't tell me.
他沒跟我說過這個
I heard you didn't do well on your mid-terms.
我聽說你期中考試考得不好
This new tutor should be able to teach you more practical strategies.
這位新家教會教你更實用的技巧
Tsuzuru.
小綴
You can have your fun.
你可以繼續你的愛好
But keep it to a minimum.
但請保持在最低限度
Okay.
好的
Namiki!
並木！
Hey!
喂！
Namiki's a little scary, but he's hot, right?
並木同學有點嚇人 但他真的很帥，是不是？
-Totally! -Right?
-沒錯！ -對吧？
I had my eye on him.
我看上他了
You think he has a girlfriend?
妳覺得他有女朋友嗎？
Don't say that!
別這麼說啊！
Oh? What's that look?
妳那是什麼表情？
Nothing!
沒什麼！
No way that's nothing!
不可能沒什麼
-It's nothing. -Tell me.
-真的沒事 -告訴我
Nice pass!
傳得好！
Namiki!
並木！
Namiki! So cool!
並木！太酷了！
Mr. Namiki.
並木先生
You okay?
你還好嗎？
Didn't you say you had plans today?
你不是說今天有安排了嗎？
Oh, crap!
糟了！
Kosshi, take care of the rest.
小志，剩下的交給你了
Sorry.
不好意思
Please.
您請
Thank you.
非常謝謝
-You okay? -Thank you very much.
-沒事吧？ -非常感謝
Thanks.
謝謝
Park Hotel, please.
請到公園酒店
Right away.
好的，馬上送您過去
Excuse me, sir. How's the Fighter's game?
不好意思 火腿鬥士隊的比賽情況怎麼樣了？
It's the top of the third, and they're beating the Carps by two.
第三局剛開始 他們領先廣島鯉魚隊兩分
I see.
知道了
I'm sorry!
抱歉！
Well, the person I'm about to meet is a big Carps fan.
因為我要見的人 是廣島鯉魚隊的狂熱粉絲
It's my girlfriend's dad.
是我女朋友的爸爸
I see.
原來如此
TSUNEMI ARIKAWA
（有川恒美）
Hello, hello.
喂
I know, I'm on my way now.
我知道，我在路上了
And I got a gift for your mom.
我也給妳媽媽買了禮物
What?
什麼？
Sorry, it was a little loud.
抱歉，這裡有點吵
Sorry.
抱歉
Let's talk later.
我們回頭再聊
Sorry, could you turn it up?
不好意思，能把音量調大嗎？
No problem.
好的
…was the flavor of cigarettes
…帶著淡淡的菸味
A bitter taste
苦澀而又令人心碎
Around this time tomorrow
明天這個時候
I wonder where you will be
不知道你會在哪裡
And who you will be thinking of
你心裡又會想著誰
You are always gonna be my love
You are always gonna be my love
If one day I ever fall in love with someone again
如果我有朝一日愛上別人
I'll remember to love You taught me how
I'll remember to love You taught me how
Could you actually go back?
可以掉頭開回去嗎？
Sorry.
非常抱歉
No, I can do that.
沒事，我可以開回去
…still a sad love song
依然唱著悲傷的情歌
Until I can sing a new one
直到我推出新的歌曲
Sorry to bother you like this.
抱歉這樣打擾妳
I know you'll probably be surprised with what I'm going to say.
我知道我要說的話可能會嚇到妳
-Ever since the opening ceremony, I-- -I'm sorry!
-從開學典禮那天起，我就… -對不起！
Huh?
什麼？
But if you want, maybe we--
但是，如果妳想的話，也許我們…
I'm flattered, thank you.
我受寵若驚，謝謝你
-I have movie tickets. -I'm sorry!
-我有電影票 -對不起！
Thank you.
老天保佑
Okay, next!
好了，下一位！
Oh man!
天啊！
Noguchi is so beautiful!
野口同學太漂亮了！
Scandalous!
太可恥了！
I heard she's dating the soccer captain though.
不過我聽說她在跟足球隊長交往
Are you for real?
你是認真的嗎？
I heard it was the class president!
我聽說她是在跟班長交往！
Oh, crap!
糟了！
You okay, Namiki?
你沒事吧，並木？
Nothing, I'm fine.
沒事，我很好
How far along are you?
您還有多久會生？
I'm due in a week.
預產期是一週後
How exciting.
真讓人期待啊
These ten months,
這十個月…
every day has felt like Christmas Eve.
每一天都感覺像聖誕夜一樣
But when I think it's almost going to end,
但我一想到這段時光即將結束
makes me a little sad.
就會覺得有點傷心
Isn't that silly, just when we can finally meet?
是不是有點傻？我們明明就要見面了
No, not at all.
不會，一點都不傻
I'm sure
我相信
every day will be Christmas after they're born.
孩子出生之後的 每一天都會像聖誕節一樣
Yae, if you'd like, these are for you.
也英，如果妳喜歡，這些可以給妳
There's no weird meaning behind this.
送花給妳沒有什麼奇怪的含義
One of my customers gave them to me.
是我的一個客人給我的
Lilacs are my favorite flowers.
我最喜歡的就是丁香花
Women just pick a man based on their status.
女生會根據男生的狀態來挑男朋友
You gotta shape up in high school.
所以你在高中一定要好好表現
Obviously, only the smart kids and jocks get all the girls in high school.
顯然只有聰明的學生和運動員 才可以得到所有高中女生的青睞
Noguchi isn't simple like that.
野口同學不是那種頭腦簡單的人
Yeah, sure, but she's got a man now.
是，沒錯，可是她現在有男朋友了
Your fault for being too chicken to ask her out.
你錯就錯在 你是個不敢找她約會的膽小鬼
Shut up!
吵死了！
Now, now. Settle down.
行了，冷靜點
This will make you feel better.
這個會讓你感覺好起來
Bonji selection Gold Award.
凡二優選金像獎得主
Welcome.
歡迎光臨
Namiki?
並木同學？
PEACH BUTT THIEF
（《蜜桃臀竊賊》）
This isn't…
這不是…
For how many days?
請問要租幾天？
Just one.
就一天
We'll watch it today.
我們今天就會看完
Who is the cutest 10-year-old in the country?
全日本最可愛的十歲女孩是誰？
Definitely my niece!
當然是我的外甥女啦！
Harumichi!
晴道！
-My cute Airu! -Harumichi!
-可愛的愛瑠！ -晴道！
She's been such a handful.
她總是這麼調皮
Lately, she doesn't want to read.
她最近都不想上學了
She'd rather do her nails.
寧可做指甲
OLYMPOS
（Olympos）
And talk about boys with bangs.
還總是在說留著劉海的男生
-What does she see in that cabbage head? -Cabbage?
-她看上那個包心菜小子什麼了？ -包心菜？
How have you been, big brother?
哥哥你最近還好嗎？
Same old, same old.
老樣子
Hey, Harumichi.
晴道
-Yes? -Where should we go?
-怎麼了？ -我們要去哪？
Anywhere you want to go!
妳想去哪就去哪！
Anywhere?!
去哪都行嗎？
Where do you want to go?
妳想去哪？
-Excuse me. -Yes?
-不好意思 -什麼事？
What size does this come in?
這雙鞋是什麼尺碼？
Welcome.
歡迎光臨
You're welcome to try it.
您可以試用一下
Thank you.
非常感謝
Here you go.
請
TSUZURU
（綴）
Is it a gift?
是要當作禮物嗎？
No.
不是的
I'm sorry.
對不起
Thank you.
非常感謝
There he is!
他來了
Tsuzuru!
小綴！
You wore that last time.
妳上次也穿這身衣服
Did I?
是嗎？
Your hair got longer, huh?
你頭髮變長了啊
Yeah.
是的
It's down to here.
都長到這下面來了
You should trim your bangs.
你應該修剪一下劉海
You shouldn't hide your face.
不要把臉遮起來
Right?
對吧？
Do you remember that shirt you liked?
還記得你喜歡的那件襯衣嗎？
The one with blue stripes.
有藍色條紋的那件
You wouldn't go out if you didn't have that.
你不穿那件衣服就不肯出門
It was tough on laundry days.
洗衣服的日子特別難過
Really?
真的嗎？
Yeah, I even have proof.
當然了，我甚至有證據
It's on video.
有影片為證
I see.
這樣啊
Ready?
好了嗎？
Thank you for the food.
我開動了
I can't eat this much.
我吃不了這麼多
It's the tastiest part.
那是最好吃的部分
How is it?
怎樣？
It's good.
很好吃
Good.
好吃
Huh? You're going out?
怎麼了？你要出去嗎？
I'll be back.
我馬上回來
Now?
現在嗎？
I'll be back by 9:00.
我9點前會回來
Bye.
再見
-Hey! -Sorry.
-喂！ -對不起
HIKARU UTADA "HATSUKOI"
（宇多田光《初戀》）
TSUZURU'S BIRTHDAY!
（小綴的生日！）
Don't tell me you stood them up?
你該不會是放他們鴿子了吧？
I got a sudden stomachache.
我突然肚子痛
It's been five years?
已經五年了嗎？
Seven.
七年了
Unbelievable.
真難以置信
Don't come crawling to me if Tsunemi dumps you.
要是恒美甩了你，你可別爬過來找我
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
行了，我知道了
-Yay! -Very cute.
-耶！ -太可愛了
What?
怎麼了？
That number.
那串數字
That's a breach of privacy.
妳這叫侵犯個人隱私
It's her birthday, isn't it?
是她的生日，對不對？
-Are you still… -It's not like…
-你還是… -不是那樣…
There's no deep meaning.
這串數字沒有別的含義
Just that nobody would figure it out if I lost it.
假如我丟了手機 這是為了防止別人猜出密碼
Uh-huh.
最好是
Harumichi!
晴道！
Airu!
愛瑠！
So cute!
太可愛了！
Thank you.
老天保佑
Ms. Noguchi!
野口同學！
Yes?
在
D-D… D…
妳…
D-Do you…
妳最喜歡…
have a favorite food?
吃什麼？
Huh?
什麼？
Never mind!
沒事了！
I got asked my favorite food.
他問我最喜歡吃什麼
I think asking someone what favorite food is
我覺得如果問別人最喜歡吃什麼
means that you like that person, right?
就代表喜歡這個人，對嗎？
Then what about you?
那並木同學你呢？
What's your favorite food?
你最喜歡吃什麼？
Me?!
我？
Naporitan.
日式拿坡里義大利麵
I see.
明白了
See you later.
晚點見
Huh?
怎麼了？
She was confessing her feelings.
她那是在跟你表白
What do you mean?
這是什麼意思？
You stupid?
你傻了嗎？
Do you understand context?
你聽不懂語境嗎？
Context.
語境
Say someone said, "I bought a bass."
假如有人說：“我買了甜不辣” i'”
But before that they mentioned, "grocery store," then this bass is…
但這人上一句說的是去日本料理店 所以“甜不辣” 是指
A fish.
關東煮
Yes.
沒錯
Before asking you your favorite food,
她問你最喜歡吃什麼之前
you were talking about how it means you like that person.
你在那大談這樣問就意味著喜歡對方
Then that's not a question, it's a confession!
所以她那不是提問，而是表白！
That's freaking context.
這就叫該死的語境
Even a high school dropout like me would know that.
連我這種高中輟學生都明白這個道理
Chicken!
膽小鬼！
Chicken.
膽小鬼
Jeez, you're late.
天啊，妳來得太晚了
Sorry.
對不起啦
The holiday's got us short-handed.
節日特別缺人手
Happy birthday, Yae
祝妳生日快樂，也英
Happy birthday, dear Yae
祝妳生日快樂，親愛的也英
There.
還有這個
Happy birthday to you
祝妳生日快樂
Congratulations, Yae.
生日快樂，也英
Thank you.
謝謝
Let me guess, leftovers from work?
讓我猜猜，這是上班拿回來的剩菜？
How rude!
真是無禮！
This is from first-class.
這可是上等品
Hideki Matsui's eaten this.
松井秀喜都吃過這個
Probably.
也許吧
Then I humbly accept.
那麼，我就開動啦
So sweet!
好甜啊！
Is it sweet?
很甜吧？
Our next song is from a new artist debuting today.
下一首歌出自今天出道的新人歌手
At the age of 15, this singer-songwriter is gaining a lot of attention.
這位唱作俱佳的 15歲新人吸引了眾多目光
This is Hikaru Utada with "Automatic."
請聽宇多田光 帶來的《Automatic》
Which means, she's the same age as you.
也就是說，她跟妳一樣大
Wow, that's impressive.
真是太驚人了
Kids these days are something else.
這年頭的小孩都這麼厲害啊
Hey.
喂
He said this was "Automatic"?
他說這歌叫《Automatic》
What does that mean?
那是什麼意思？
Moves on its own.
自動
On its own?
自動？
Ah, speaking of moving on its own,
哎呀，說到自動
the vending machine at the factory just raised their prices.
工廠裡的自動販賣機漲價了
I know the sales tax went up to five percent,
我也知道消費稅漲了百分支五
but how does a 100-yen coffee suddenly jump up to 120 yen?
可是100日元的咖啡 怎麼可以突然漲到120日元啊？
Mommy!
媽媽！
I'll spin you around. Give me your hand.
我帶妳轉圈圈，把手給我
Give me your hand, let's spin!
把手給我，我們轉圈圈吧！
Look this way!
看這邊！
There's a big one stuck here.
這裡卡住了一大塊
A big one?
一大塊？
Look! See?
看！看到沒？
ARE YOU ON YOUR WAY HOME? ARE YOU OKAY?
（要回來了嗎？沒事吧？）
Could you head towards the national route?
不好意思，您能開到國道去嗎？
LIVESTREAM STARTED
（直播已開始）
Sir, is this the TV tower?
先生，這是電視塔嗎？
I'm not sure.
我不清楚
It's the TV tower from the north side of the 12.
這是從正北方拍到的電視塔
Could you take a u-turn there and head towards Sapporo?
不好意思，您能掉頭往札幌開嗎？
Ishikari Kaido is closed,
石狩街道那邊封路了
so please go south on the one way street on 3rd and head to Kitaichijo.
請沿第三大道單行線往南開 再從基督教堂繞過去
Okay…
-好的 -好
Right there.
就是那邊
HIKARU UTADA "HATSUKOI"
（宇多田光《初戀》）
I'm sorry.
對不起
How did you find me?
妳是怎麼找到我的？
A taxi driver's instincts?
因為計程車司機的直覺？
And sorry.
我也很抱歉
I looked at your friend's Instagram.
我看了你朋友的Instagram
Your girlfriend?
是你女朋友嗎？
She probably just thinks I'm a fan who hits like on all her posts.
她可能只把我當成一個 給她所有發文按讚的粉絲吧
I thought I could meet her here.
我還以為能在這裡見到她
I was too late.
我來得太晚了
She's lovely, isn't she?
她很可愛呢
Here, before I forget.
給你，趁我還沒忘
I didn't know what to get you.
我不知道該送你什麼
Happy birthday.
生日快樂
Thank you.
謝謝
What? You want me to listen?
怎麼？你想給我聽嗎？
What is this?
這是什麼？
It's beautiful.
旋律很美
I wrote it with her in mind.
我一邊想著她一邊寫的
This?!
這首嗎？
You made it?! This?! That's amazing!
這是你寫的？太棒了！
That's so amazing!
太厲害了！
Anybody could make this.
誰都能寫這種東西
No they couldn't!
才不是呢！
This is amazing!
這太棒了！
You're a genius!
你是個天才！
Wow!
太強了！
Anyone can make it.
誰都能寫出來
I love this song.
我喜歡這首歌
Best song this year.
年度最佳單曲
Best this year?
年度最佳？
Three lucky requesters will be selected at random
將會隨機抽取三位幸運申請者
to win an official sticker.
贏得官方貼紙
This special draw was only announced yesterday, but…
這次特別抽獎昨天才剛宣布，但…
Stop! Drop me off here!
停車，讓我在這裡下車！
What? You're being crazy. Not yet.
什麼？妳瘋了嗎？還沒到呢
What is it?
怎麼回事？
What?
怎麼了？
Namiki?
並木同學？
What's wrong?
出什麼事了？
You'll catch a cold.
你會感冒的
Namiki?
並木同學？
What about you, Noguchi?
那妳呢，野口同學？
What?
什麼？
What is…
野口同學…
your favorite food?
妳最喜歡吃什麼？
What is it?
是什麼？
Shrimp.
蝦
I like you.
我喜歡妳
Ever since we first met.
從我們第一次見面時就喜歡了
Please…
請妳…
go out with me.
跟我交往吧
Okay.
好的
Me too.
我也是
Namiki, I…
並木同學…
like you too.
我也喜歡你
…was the flavor of cigarettes
帶著淡淡的菸味
A bitter taste
苦澀而又令人心碎
Hey.
我說
You little punk ass.
你這個小混蛋
If you're gonna smoke, be more sneaky about it.
要是想抽菸，就藏得更隱蔽一點
Yes, ma'am.
遵命
And also…
還有…
Just promise me one thing.
答應我一件事
Bring her back before midnight no matter what.
無論如何，午夜之前都要送她回來
If you knock her up, I'll kill you.
你要是把她肚子搞大了，我會殺了你
Yes, ma'am!
遵命！
I'll remember to love You taught me how
I'll remember to love You taught me how
You are always gonna be the one
You are always gonna be the one
Now, it is still a sad love song
我現在依然唱著悲傷的情歌
Until I can sing a new one
直到我推出新的歌曲
Time, standing still
停滯不前的時光
is about to start moving
即將開始轉動
So many things I don't want to forget
有那麼多事想永遠銘記在心
I'll do that.
我來弄吧
-Oh, okay then. Thanks. -No prob.
-好，謝謝 -不客氣
Around this time tomorrow
明天這個時候
I know I will be crying
我將哭泣不已
I will be thinking of you
想念我深深愛過的你
You will always be inside my heart
You will always be inside my heart
There will always a place just for you
I hope that I have a place in your heart too
Nakajima Park, please.
請到中島公園
Right away.
馬上送您過去
Now and forever you are still the one
Now and forever you are still the one
Now, it is still a sad love song
我現在依然唱著悲傷的情歌
Until I can sing a new one
直到我推出新的歌曲
You are always gonna be my love
You are always gonna be my love
If one day I fall in love with someone again…
如果我有朝一日愛上別人…
Actually, turn here!
麻煩您，請在這裡轉彎！
Follow that taxi!
請跟著那輛計程車！
-It's too late, sir. -Hurry!
-先生，已經太晚了 -快點！
I'll have to take another lap.
我要再繞一圈才可以
You are always gonna be my love
You are always gonna be my love
Every moment…
每一個瞬間…
is an irreplaceable piece of our lives.
都是一片獨一無二的人生拼圖
But what if…
但如果…
you lose an important piece?
弄丟了最重要的那一片，該怎麼辦？
ALL SONGS WRITTEN AND COMPOSED HERSELF! DEBUT ALBUM
（所有歌曲均由她親自作詞作曲！ 出道專輯！）
HIKARU UTADA'S LONG-AWAITED 1ST ALBUM FIRST LOVE
（宇多田光備受期待的首張專輯 《First Love》）
12 SONGS INCLUDING "AUTOMATIC"!
（包括《Automatic》在內 共有12首歌）
OUR TIME HAS STARTED NOW
（我們的時代已經開啟）
Subtitle translation by: Zensho Yamamoto
字幕翻譯：小澤